Day 3 of 7 working in social.
This job is fun,
fun,
but um,
is it also 1 little
lonely sometimes,
isn't it?
Today I have done 3 interviews
to add 1 new person to the social team
and the 3 agreed that
1 of the things they miss the most is some ideas,
sharing problems.
And the truth is that it's not the first time I've heard it,
is that I stew it,
I eat it,
when we do face-to-face events or training
is one of the most repeated phrases.
And I understand it because 1 part of the creative process
is inevitably solo
has to be.
There is 1 part of thinking,
write,
decide or think about 1 idea you make
you alone and it's okay.
But that's one thing
and it is quite another to always work like this.
In the end,
people are very grateful to work as a team,
to listen to other realities,
to help each other,
contrast. And even we,
who are several in the team,
are several in the team.
we have had to set up spaces for this,
talk without further ado,
without status,
without customers,
without everything having to end in 1 task in ClickUp.
Do you mean anything else?
What beautiful nails!
And yet I am still surprised that no one is promoting
more community
among people in the sector.
Let's see if we're going to have to put together something that apparently
being surrounded by content does not mean being accompanied